<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Strategy on Think Ahead: The Stratify Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.stratifyplan.com/categories/strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Strategy on Think Ahead: The Stratify Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.8</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.stratifyplan.com/categories/strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Get More Done with Fewer Decisions: The Power of Pre-Planning</title>
      <link>https://blog.stratifyplan.com/posts/get-more-done-with-pre-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stratifyplan.com/posts/get-more-done-with-pre-planning/</guid>
      <description>Discover how pre-planning eliminates decision fatigue and boosts daily productivity. Learn strategies for focus and flow using strategic planning techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Blocking vs Task Lists: Which One Actually Works?</title>
      <link>https://blog.stratifyplan.com/posts/time-blocking-vs-task-lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stratifyplan.com/posts/time-blocking-vs-task-lists/</guid>
      <description>Explore the pros and cons of time blocking vs task lists — and learn how to combine them for maximum productivity without confusion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Focus: Top Apps to Block Dopamine Triggers and Boost Productivity</title>
      <link>https://blog.stratifyplan.com/posts/apps_that_block_dopamine_triggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stratifyplan.com/posts/apps_that_block_dopamine_triggers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s hyper-connected world, distractions are just a click away, making it increasingly difficult to maintain focus and productivity. With notifications constantly vying for our attention, our brains get frequent hits of dopamine—the neurotransmitter responsible for pleasure and reward. While dopamine is crucial for motivation and learning, constant exposure to dopamine triggers can lead to procrastination and decreased productivity. Fortunately, technology offers a solution: apps designed to help block these distractions and keep your attention on what truly matters.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
